Yes, sir.
Are we live?
Okay, we're live from here.
Yes, sir.
Today, too, we are in high spirits.
Let's work together
Go, go, go, go!
Don't get too hard. You'll lose if you do.
I love it! I love it! It's started!
So today, we're going to continue with the program.
Let's see, shall we?
Well, let's see some pictures... you all really love cameras, don't you?
That's right.
Say "bye-bye" to all the pictures you're taking.
Yes, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
Yes, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
You're welcome to send them to us.
The photo of the flower path. By the way, you can only see the thumbnail now.
It looks like food. It's always food.
First of all, let's go to No. 1.
Oh, look at that!
This is "Shukumeruri"... The one that Hanamichi is falling down hard, right?
That's right, I'm addicted to Matsuya. The reason I became addicted to Matsuya is this Shkumerli.
But it's not on sale anymore... Oh, I see... But it's very tasty. It's a Georgia dish.
Georgia? Georgian food. Where? Where? - Ex-Georgia.
Georgian? How do you know? Georgia's kind of an anglicized version of Georgia. Georgia.
Georgia? That's Georgia?
It's a cream stew with a lot of garlic. It's like sweet potatoes, but with a lot more garlic.
I ate it for about a week straight. So people in Georgia can eat a lot of dishes with garlic, right?
I'm really addicted to it! Scomelloli! How come you're following Matsuyama's amazing place again?
I wish I could try it.
I've been pushing it a lot, and I got a lot of letters about it, and I ate that thing Hanamichi is pushing right now.
He wrote so much and pressed it. And another one...
What are you doing?
Champignon hamburger steak?
This one too!
I've already received a third, and it's in my personal fashion.
I'm sure you can imagine what it's supposed to taste like.
It's a hamburger steak, but it doesn't taste like a hamburger steak.
It doesn't taste like a hamburger, it doesn't taste like a hamburger, it tastes like a hamburger.
It's like an Italian demi-glace sauce.
It's not a hamburger steak in the image of Italian demi-glace sauce.
It looks like it, but it's not.
It's a little bit sour, so it goes really well with cheese.
By the way, there's another one, but as expected.
I'm sure you're right... it's good, isn't it?
I don't think it's serious, right?
I've seen this logo before.
I've seen this logo before on Malaysian food, beef stew, and for a limited time only.
I've had 3 in a row at Matsuya... how many days have I been talking about this?
I've never been to a set meal restaurant like this before, so when I tried this limited time offer, I realized how good Matsuya was.
I've never been to a set meal restaurant like this before, so this limited time offer made me realize how delicious Matsuya's food is.
I want to be in a commercial.
I'll go eat it right away. I'll go eat it right away.
I'll go right away. I didn't ask for it, but it'll come.
I didn't ask for it, but it showed up.
Matsuya is good, isn't it?
Gyuudon usually comes with miso soup.
It's great, isn't it? Only at Matsuya.
That's for sure
Well, well, well, well...
I've been to Matsuya 3 times in a row...
I've sent you two photos, too, Mr. Matsunaga.
First of all, it's a little timely...
I went to the Suzuka Circuit in Mie Prefecture to see the F1 race.
I saw it!
Wow, I saw it live!
I saw it live.
It was so exciting!
There's a race called F1.
It's the best car race in the world.
There's a car race, and it was held in Japan just a few days ago.
The Japanese Grand Prix?
That's right.
I went to see it, and this is the second picture, but I brought a telephoto lens.
This is the F1 race, and there are 20 F1 drivers, but only one is Japanese.
And this is his car.
Does he drive this car? Yes. He's already going 100, 200 kilometers per hour.
Yes, he's driving very fast. I'd like to take some pictures.
I worked really hard. I was taking pictures.
I was taking pictures.
We're close. - Really?
but I'd like to be friends with him... but he's a veteran... and he's not hiding it... but yes... he's a friend.
But this is a little bit geeky, but you can walk on the circuit where they are running.
You can actually walk on the track, but we've got something really cool here.
What is it, what is it, what is it, what is it, what is it, what is it, what is it, what is it?
I'm sorry, this is a little bit geeky.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
What's this?
This way. Thank you.
Do you know what it is?
Kelp?
It's a little black.
Can you tell?
Kelp.
This way.
Is that from the tire?
Yes, that's right.
Kelp!
I've got a few tires, and I'm a bit of a geek, but...
For an F1 fan, this is just outrageous, outrageous, outrageous...
F1 tires are very high quality and edible.
What? Really? You can eat them. They're totally edible. What do you mean, totally edible?
Is it good at all?
Want some? Eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it? Eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it. Is it good?
Does it taste like rubber? No, well, you just have to try some.
Why are you eating it? It's really good.
It's good. Want to try some? Is this a tire? Really? You want to try it? Yes, please.
It tastes like, um... sakiika... like this.
Don't worry, don't worry. It's totally fine.
What do you think?
It tastes like chub mackerel.
Delicious! It's sakiika!
It's like the F1 soy sakiquid.
It's saki squid.
So...
I'm going to play a little ignorant trick on you.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me!
I thought you were crazy.
I'm selling something called a "tire cusk squid" here.
When I saw this.
I wanted to surprise you guys.
Oh, man!
He fell for it.
Mr. Yoshida and I got together for a minute.
It looks so realistic.
I was really surprised.
Whoever thought of this is amazing.
It's so interesting.
I'm sure it's fallen. It's probably like this.
I was fooled.
Isasumi's black.
Isasumi black Isasumi? Good, but it's super tasty.
It's so good!
When I ate it, I thought the radiation was bad.
I thought it was an on-air accident.
Yay!
I see...
I bought souvenirs from Mie Prefecture for the two of them.
The very same one from Suzuka.
It was a little F1-related, so...
I'm out.
Here's one for the master.
I had this at a ryokan we went to and it was really good. I got some Ise Udon. I love it.
This is... you know... local udon... but it's really soft.
Here you go.
Rather than eating it in soup, they eat it without pouring soy sauce or other sauce on it.
It's good. I wonder if it's made from tire shavings.
It's good, too.
And here's Mr. Hanamichi.
Thank you!
Speaking of Mie, this is great beef!
Matsuzaka beef! Matsuzaka beef stew. I knew it!
Matsuzaka beef is famous in Mie. Amazing!
What do you like with this?
I'll eat it. Thank you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry I startled you.
No, no, no... I made a surprise for you.
He's lost his mind.
He really has lost his mind.
And when he said he could eat it, it was so refreshing.
So I thought for sure he's lost his mind.
He's out of his mind.
I thought he was okay.
I was worried.
For a moment.
Then I ate it, and it tasted exactly like saki squid.
That's why they call it a tire.
I thought it might be a little bit like that when it's heated up.
And also...
F1 tires are the highest quality, so maybe it's natural rubber?
I'm thinking maybe it's safe to put it in your mouth... but they don't use natural rubber for F1 tires, do they?
I'm sure it's fine to put it in your mouth.
It's a good idea.
I'm giving an award to the person who thought of this.
It's so great!
That's why I want it.
I want one of these, I'll do it, I'll give it to somebody, really, and Hanamichi got one for his tire gas.
I'm sure it'll catch on with the members.
So, now that we're talking about cars, Hanamichi also drives a Mercedes Benz.
The Mercedes Benz that you all saw with such emotion is here in the studio today.
I've never seen a tire like this before.
I've seen it up close and personal... and it's really solid... and it's really good... and it's really good... and it's really good... and it's really good... and it's really good! This is an Armorgae! And what is the highest level of Armorgae, the Bercedes bench? Please put Tacchi in. He didn't put it in. He didn't put it in.
I put a fresh note in here. It smells like the ocean when you open it. It's great. The manufacturer's red brakes are really cool, like Brembo or something like that.
It's really smooth, really soft... is it for kids?
I wonder if Mercedes-Benz supervised it a little?
Mercedes, Mercedes, it really is made by Mercedes!
The wheels are shining!
but he achieved his goal... right?
I want him to come up here and do this... and then he says "dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn, dahn".
Like a child with a temper tantrum.
Well, well, well... we'd better get started on the live broadcast.
I'm sure it was a big hit with everyone.
I think everyone will be very happy. I'm really crazy.
I thought so. I'm sure everyone thought so.
I thought it wouldn't make it on the air.
They're all in a hurry!
Mobilityland really made this! It's so clever!
But the fact that the master ate it right away is amazing!
You thought he was going to eat it? I'm a quick eater. I wondered what rubber tastes like.
I've never tasted anything like it. It's so interesting.
It's so funny. Everyone's fooled.
There's a warning on it.
It's an exquisite delicacy made from saki squid, colored with squid ink.
Don't mistake it for real tire castings.
Mr. Tanami received a devil's charge for his Mercedes on the way to Hanamichi.
Type 99 received a Devil Charge with a stamp of congratulations!
Congratulations to Yuuhi Zadar on his graduation.
Isn't this it? A present!
Congratulations to Mr. Yuuhi Zadar for being the owner of a Mercedes Benz!
Thank you very much!
Let's get on with it.
Come to think of it, I don't have any plans to go to school... for now.
I don't have any plans to go to school at the moment.
On the contrary, go!
Please go!
Go to college or something.
How's it going? I think it's still spring break.
What do you think? If I was in school, wouldn't you miss it?
It's better to go all the time. For 10 years or so.
Now I'm thinking of buying a class in something I like to do, like English conversation.
Maybe I'll go to driving school.
I'd like you to take a picture of the normal side of me.
I'd love to see you in a bigger Mercedes.
A real one.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well.
See you next week.
8:00 p.m.
I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for watching today.
Thank you very much.
What applause.
And your wife.
Thank you very much for watching.